Karl Francis Alberto

Studying Coding, Cloud & Cybersecurity

Coder Academy - 2021

karlfalberto@gmail.com karl.alberto@hotmail.com

0408 294 824

I have extensive experience in customer service management, as well as a background in traditional marketing and advertising. Technology has always been one of my passions, and I feel I am ready to expand my career horizons and step into a role within the IT industry.

SKILLS

- Customer service experience social media, live chat, email ticket systems, etc.
- Tech focused, adaptable to new/varied systems
- Extensive knowledge and experience with various social media platforms (including third party tools)
- Social media marketing and advertising; including market research background
- Impeccable grammar and spelling
- Fluent conversational Tagalog (Filipino)

EXPERIENCE

Harvey Norman Online, Homebush West, NSW - Customer Service Team Leader - Social Media AUGUST 2011 - JULY 2012, JULY 2013 - PRESENT

- Mixed marketing and customer service management role for social media at the launch of eCommerce for Harvey Norman
- Transitioned into a full-fledged customer service role as Team Leader in 2013, managing a small team dedicated to social media customer service
- Manage Google and Facebook locations for all Harvey Norman stores nationwide
- Customer review moderation via BazaarVoice and Google My Business platforms

Generic Publications (GP Advertising), Homebush West, NSW - Advertising Coordinator

JULY 2010 - JULY 2011, JULY 2012 - JULY 2013 (Company/role restructure)

- Started as an Advertising Trainee at Harvey Norman's in-house advertising agency
- Managed production of catalogues and press adverts across Harvey Norman brands, for Australia, New Zealand and Ireland
- Trained as a Copywriter for catalogue copywriting
- Started managing and moderating Harvey Norman's online customer service system; including Facebook and Twitter

I-View Pty. Ltd., North Sydney, NSW

Data-Entry Operator, Team Leader MARCH 2007 - JULY 2010 Australia Post - Sydney Gateway Facility, Clyde, NSW

Mail/Parcel Post Office (Christmas Casual)
DEC 2005 - JAN 2006, DEC 2004 - FEB 2005,
NOV 2003 - JAN 2004

EDUCATION

TAFE, Sydney Institute, Ultimo - Advanced Diploma of Advertising - 2009

TAFE, Western Sydney Institute, Blacktown - Diploma in Business Advertising - 2006

TAFE, Western Sydney Institute, Blacktown - Diploma in Business Marketing - 2006